A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1982-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1982-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.851
This collection consists of 16,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1986 Feb 11-16.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files and administrative committee files, 1982-1983; and, permanent files, 1965-1984.
Permanent records concern: the Miller Center; the Center for Advanced Studies; the Development Capital Campaign; Southeastern University Association for Physics; and, ad hoc and special building committees.
Organization
Series I: General Records, 1982-1983 Boxes 1-23
Series II: Administrative Committees, 1982-1983 Boxes 23-24
Series III: Permanent Files, 1965-1984 Boxes 25-39
Series IV: Restricted Material Box 40
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous--Albemarle Garden Club-Morea, Alpha Kappa Alpha 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous--American Association of University Women, Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - "An-Az" Miscellaneous--Cypriot Pottery, Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Administration 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Admissions-Law 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association--General--Reunions, List of Alumni Children 1982 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Professors 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education--ABA Accreditation, Committee on Athletic 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Anthropology 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Architecture 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Art--General 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Asian Studies 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Associated Western Universities 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Colleges 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities (1 of 4) 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities--National Institutes of Health (NIH) Reauthorization Bill, Military Recruiting on Campus, Linking of Financial Aid and Registration for the Draft, Integrity of Research (2-4 of 4) 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges--D.O.D 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--General--Ralph Sampson, TV Contracts 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--ACC 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--CFA--Football Television and the Antitrust Act 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--NCAA 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Attorney General 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Auditor--Internal 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - "Ba-Bm" Miscellaneous--Gift of Cypriot Pre-Classical Pottery to Bayly Museum, Capital Campaign, Student Housing, Black Student Alliance 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - "Bn-Br" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Sigma Chi accident 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - "Bs-Bz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Fall Convocation Speech of Josiah Bunting III (President of Hampden-Sydney), Commonwealth Day 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Biology 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Business and Finance 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Business and Finance--Executive Planning Group 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - "Ca-Cg" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Camp Foundation--Establishment of the Andrew D. Hart Endowed Chair in Internal Medicine, Center for Law and National Security, Center for Oceans Law and Policy 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - "Ch-Cn" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Chevrolet Scholarship Program, Chi Phi--Safety, University of Chicago, Youth Goodwill Mission of the Republic of China, Conflict of Interests Act, Pre- Classical Cypriot Pottery Gift, Chronicle of Higher Education, Clemson University--Sanctions 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - "Co-Cz" Miscellaneous--Committee on Concerned Scientists--Revocation of Academic Degrees in USSR, Capital Campaign, Council for Advancement and Support of Education, Council on the Environment- -University Houses (Morea), Cyprus 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Cavalier Daily 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Chemistry 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Civil Rights 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Classics 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Clinch Valley College--General--Coal Strip-Mining by Price Land Company 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - College Board 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Commerce 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Comptroller--State 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Computing and Communications 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Congress--Student Aid and Draft Registration 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Consortia--Northern Virginia 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Consortia--Valley 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Consortia--Western 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education--Summer on the Lawn 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Council of Presidents 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Council of Southern Universities 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - "Da-De" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Norman Darden Books, Arthur Voning Davis Foundation, Delta Psi--"Billy Hill Memorial Relay Race" 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, UVA Hospital Funds, DuPont 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Darden School--Capital Campaign, Accreditation, Darden School Program evaluation, MBA Program, AIESC 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Darden Business Sponsors 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Dean's Meetings 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Development--General 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - "E" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), U.S. Department of Education, State Office of Emergency and Energy Services, Exxon Education Fund 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Education 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Energy Policy Studies Center 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--Elis Olsson Memorial Foundation, Prime Computer, Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--Industrial Productivity Conference (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Buildings--State 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - English 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Enrollment--General 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Environmental Sciences 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Equal Opportunity Office 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - "F" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, FBI, Federal Emergency Management Agency, Figgie International, Ford Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Faculty--General 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Food Services 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - French 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - "G" Miscellaneous--Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), Gandalf Data Inc., Capital Campaign, General Electric, George Mason University, Easters, Gould Inc., Commonwealth Day, Gulf Oil Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly--Salary Increases, Indigent Care Appropriation Amendment, UVA Hospital, Housing, Alumni in Georgia, Appropriations, Evaluation of action Team Process at UVA (2 of 3) 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly (3 of 3) 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summaries 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - General Services 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - German 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants "A-G" 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants "H-P" 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants "Q-Z" 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Administration 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Commerce and Resources 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Education 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Office--General--Funding, Critical Re-Evaluation of Virginia State Government, Equal Opportunity, Capital Campaign, Charter Day Address--College of William and Mary, Manufacturing Developments in Virginia year 1982, Industrial Productivity Conference, Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Office--Human Resources 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Task Force on Science and Technology 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Office--Transportation and General Safety 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Office--Washington Liaison Office 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--Commission on Career Opportunities 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - "H" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), Anna Arnold Hedgeman, Hewlett Packard Hillman Foundation, House of Delegates 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - History 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Honor System 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Housing 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - "I" Miscellaneous--IBM, State Division of Industrial Development, Institute of European Studies, Institute of International Education, IFC, International Council for Equal Opportunity Principles, Invesco Capital Management Inc., Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Institute of Government 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - International Studies 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - "J" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, James Madison University, Jefferson Scholars, Jones Foundation, Judiciary Committee 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - "K" Miscellaneous--Cyprus, Capital Campaign, Kellogg Foundation, Kennedy Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - "L" Miscellaneous--Cyprus, Capital Campaign, Luce Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Law School--General--Capital Campaign, ABA, Journal of Law and Politics, Judges' Program 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Lawn Society 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Legal Advisor 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Library 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Presidential Campaign, University of Madras, Anna Manahan, Meade Scholarships, Mellon Bank, Mellon Fellowships, Mellon Foundation, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Merill Lynch & Co. Inc 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - "Mi-Mz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Monsanto Fund, Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Menzies Memorial Trust 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Marine Science--National Sea Grant Program 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Mariners Museum (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Material Management 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Mathematics 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--General 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--General 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--Personnel 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--General 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--Personnel 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Music 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - "N" Miscellaneous--National Research Council, Norfolk Academy, Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges--General (NASULGC) 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges--International Letters (NASULGC) 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - National Science Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - "O" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Overlook 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - "Pa-Ph" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, PepsiCo Foundation Inc, Phi Beta Kappa, Phi Delta Theta, Phillip Morris Inc, Phillips Petroleum Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - "Pi-Pz" Miscellaneous--Pi Kappa Alpha, Pi Kappa Phi, Potomac River Basin Consortium, Prime Computer 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Parking and Transportation 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Personnel 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - Personnel and Training (State) 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Philosophy 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Physical Plant 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Physics 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Planning--Project Status Reports 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay (Project Narrative) 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--State 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Planning and Budget--University 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Promotions 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Provost 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Research 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Psychology 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Purchases and Supply 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - "R" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Radioactive Waste Management Commission, Ronald Reagan, Recording for the Blind, Reynolds Metals Co. Foundation, Risk Management and Safety, Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea) 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Recommendations 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Registrar 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Religious Studies 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Risk Management and Safety 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--General 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Army 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Navy 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - "Sa-Sh" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Lord Scarman, Schering Corp., Shell Companies Foundation, Shenandoah College and Conservatory of Music 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - "Si-Sn' Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Sloan Foundation, Shenandoah College and Conservatory of Music, Alson H. Smith Jr. 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - "So" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Society of Fellows, Society of Cincinnati, Sohio, Solid Waste Commission, Solomon Amendment, South Africa, Southern Regional Education Board 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - "Sp-Sz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Spanish House, Sperry Corporation, Squibb Institute for medical research, State Employees' Credit Union, State Police, Thomas I. Storrs 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Sociology 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Space and Energy Management 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Speeches--Current 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Sponsored Programs 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE) (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Council Notes (SCHE) 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - State Department of Education 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - State Fire Marshall 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs (1 of 2) 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs (2 of 2) 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Student Council (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Summer Session 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous--Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), Tandy Corporation, Department of Taxation, TIAA/CREF, Department of Telecommunications, Tenneco, Texaco, Texas Instruments Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - "Tf-Tz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Travel Invoices 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - "U" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, U.S. Army, U.S. Department of Labor, U.S. Postal Services, U.S. Trust 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - United States Savings Bonds 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - United Way 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Universities Research Association 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Guides 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Journal 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Press 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Relations 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Union 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - University Police 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - "V" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, O.M. Vicars, Cyprus, Vincent Estate, Virginia Association of Student Financial Aid Administration, Vepco, Virginia Historic Landmark Commission, Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - "Wa-Wh" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, John W. Warner, Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), Westinghouse 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous--Capital Campaign, Housing--Sprigg Lane (Morea), Williamsburg, Women's Alliance 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous--Ylvisaker, Capital Campaign 1982-1983 (Box 23)
- Series II: Administrative Committees
  - General 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Admissions 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Afro-American Affairs 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Algernon Sydney Darden 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Arboretum 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Architectural Advisory 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Athletic Advisory 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Bayly Museum 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Calendar 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Cemetery 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Chapel 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Chemical and Biological Hazards Safety 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittees--Processions 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittees--Public Occasions 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Community Colleges 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Computers 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Development Steering 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Education and Employment Opportunities, Obligations and Rights 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Energy Conservation 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Fulbright Grants 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Graphics 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Gwathmey Award 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Housing 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - International Students 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Lectures--Page, Barbour, and Richard 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Library 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Master Plan 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Names 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Proxy Advisory 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Radiation Safety 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Radiation Safety--Subcommittee--Radioactive Drug Research 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Registration 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Residential Life 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - ROTC 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Scheduling 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Employment, and Loans 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Security and General Safety 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Student Activities 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Student Health 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Summer Grants 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Summer Sessions 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Traffic Appeals 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Traffic and Parking 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Truman Scholarships 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - University Committee on Students 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - University Press 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - University Union 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Status on University Students 1982-1983 (Box 24)
- Series III: Permanent Files
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1970Nov-1978Dec (Box 25)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Advisory Board and Appointments (2 folders) 1965Apr-1977Nov (Box 25)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Memberships in Center 1970Nov-1978Dec (Box 25)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Memberships in Center, Part II (2 folders) 1979Jan-1981Dec (Box 26)
  - Development/Alumni Data System (2 folders) 1978 Jan30 (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Analysis of Projects 1977Dec-1978Jan (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Announcement of Campaign Literature 1981Dec-1982Jan (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--General 1983Jan-1984Apr (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Atlanta 1983Jun-1984May (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Baltimore 1983-1985 (Box 26)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Boston 1984 Aug-Oct (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Charlottesville 1983 Sep-Nov (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Houston, Lynchburg, Miami 1983May-1984Jun (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Louisville 1983Dec-1984Apr (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--New Orleans 1983Jun-1984Jun (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--New York 1983Sep-1984Dec (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Palm Beach 1983Mar-1984Jun (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Philadelphia 1984 Jun-Oct (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Richmond 1983 Apr-Oct (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Roanoke 1983Jan-1984May (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--South Carolina 1984 Apr-May (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Tidewater 1983Mar-1984Jan (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Washington, D.C. 1984 Mar-Jun (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign Area Campaign--Wilmington, Del. 1983 Jul-Nov (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Bio/Financial Data 1981 Mar-Apr (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Reports 1980Apr-1981Nov (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Communications Committee 1981Jul-1984Oct (Box 27)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Corporate Committee (2 folders) 1981Jul-1984Oct (Box 28)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Corporate Data 1981Jul-1984Oct (Box 28)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Foundation Cash/ Pledge Reports 1981 Jun 3 (Box 28)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Foundation Committee 1981Apr-1984Nov (Box 28)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--General I (1 of 3) 1979Nov-1981Dec (Box 28)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--General I (2-3 of 3) 1979Nov-1981Dec (Box 29)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--General II (2 folders) 1982Jan-1983May (Box 29)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Internal Development Group 1981Jul-1984Oct (Box 29)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Interview Letters 1980 Jun-Sep (Box 29)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Major Gifts Committee 1981Apr-1984Oct (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--National Alumni/ Parents Committee 1981Nov-1984Oct (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--National Chairman 1981Mar-1984Oct (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Needs List 1980May-1981Oct (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Organizing Committee 1981Sep-1985Feb (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Prospects 1980Sep-1983Apr (Box 30)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--Steering Committee (2 folders) 1981Sep-1985Feb (Box 31)
  - Development--Capital Campaign--V.P. Candidate Team Members 1980Jul-1981Apr (Box 31)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (3 folders) 1975-1977 (Box 31)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (5 folders) 1977-1988 (Box 32)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (5 folders) 1980-1983 (Box 33)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (2 folders) 1983-1984 (Box 34)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs--Ad Hoc Committee 1970Mar-1973Mar (Box 34)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs--Barco (2 folders) 1972Oct-1975Apr (Box 34)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs--Institute of National Policy Studies 1975 Jun-Jul (Box 34)
  - Physics (NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) I 1980 May-Jun (Box 35)
  - Physics (NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) II (2 folders) 1980 Jun-Dec (Box 35)
  - Physics(NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) III (2 folders) 1981 Jan-Dec (Box 35)